and One of the good things about
whatever your first draft is is that
you've
actually done this at all, right?
So you've actually you've actually
written something you've bothered to
start
I read an article by somebody who had
decided he wanted to be a writer and
he went about it in a very interesting
way in that he contacted the publisher
and Rather than saying oh, here's my
book.
He said can you Send me all of the
books that you've been
sent over the last year I volunteered
to read your slush pile.
That's what it's called And he said
one of the things that he found really
interesting
about that. He read a hundred books in
a year is That a lot of them
even they might be in the right length
But they were unfinished They
they were kind of you know, they they
weren't they were half -assed or they
were
like Seven eighths asked or whatever,
but they weren't finished They had
somebody
hadn't put all of the effort into into
them that they needed to be put into
them
to make them feel that they were
finished